#### PRODUCT MARKETING MANAGER

### Senior Marketing Professional

Versatile senior marketing professional with over 15 years of B2B and B2C healthcare marketing experience within corporate and not-for-profit environments. Successful in applying a critical mix of strategic thinking, attention to detail, relationship building, creativity and enthusiasm to achieve business goals.

### Areas of Expertise

- Communications
- New and Enhanced Product Launches
- Marketing Campaigns
- Agency/Vendor Management
- Project Management
- Sales Enablement

- Event Planning and Promotion
- Competitive Analysis
- Collateral Management
- Website Management
- Brand Management
- Strategic Leadership

### Professional Experience

Product Marketing Manager 10/2006 to Current Autodesk Inc. Minnesota, GA

- Develop and execute product go-to-market plans for key health and wellness programs, in collaboration with product management, training and sales stakeholders.
- Oversee marketing communications schedule to efficiently monitor outreach timing, frequency and delivery.
- Manage the creation and delivery of communications to prospects, clients and consultants.
- Create sales collateral, presentations, proposals and website content in collaboration with stakeholders to promote the brand and increase awareness.
- Develop, support and execute lead generation processes and campaigns to effectively track leads, fill sales pipeline and generate revenue.
- Identify and execute process improvements to ensure effective and timely communication of product enhancements, system downtimes and organization updates.
- Collaborate with market research vendors and internal stakeholders to develop and release competitive intelligence tools and information to stakeholders.

#### Notable Achievements: Â

- Launched an interactive, sales enablement platform that provides sellers access to relevant, customizable assets in alignment with the sales
  process.
- Drove go-to-market strategy to launch new health coaching platform, resulting in 30 client migrations and \$2.7MM in new sales within the first six months.
- Executed the redesign and launch of the company's website within budget and timing constraints.
- Launched the organization's first multi-modal lead generation campaigns, including a "Top Chef" conference series that drew attendance valued at \$27MM in potential revenue.

# Communications Specialist 09/2002 to 08/2006 Cooley Reston, VA

- Managed the creation and delivery of communications to members, clients and consultants.
- Partnered with creative agencies and area printers in the creation, print and delivery of collateral (e.g., member newsletters, annual reports, provider directories and direct mailers).
- Launched the plan's first consumer-driven insurance products into the marketplace.
- Coordinated print, television and radio promotions of new clinic facilities, physicians and services.
- Collaborated with executives and medical staff to compose speeches and presentations.
- Coordinated plan-sponsored open houses, annual meetings, health fairs and public relations activities.

#### Notable Achievements: Â

- Developed and executed promotion strategies for grand opening of the plan's largest full-service clinic and complementary medicine services.
- Redesigned the Provider Directory to enhance member education on network and coverage options to reduce overall plan costs.
- Executed promotional campaign to generate member and community awareness for the plan's 30th anniversary celebration.

# Marketing Specialist 10/1999 to 08/2002 Emerald Expositions Louisville, KY

- Developed and managed inventory of benefit design options and associated member materials.
- Quality control liaison for accurate and timely processing of new business and client renewal forms.
- Communicated client or plan-driven benefit design changes to stakeholders, clients and members.
- Developed, filed and maintained plan certificates of coverage with the Wisconsin Office of the Commissioner of Insurance to ensure compliance with state mandates and regulations.

Notable Achievements: Â

- Transitioned member enrollment material inventory to print-on-demand process to improve productivity and reduce storage/print costs.
- Developed and executed sales and marketing workflows to support the plan's successful transition to an integrated electronic medical record and payer platform.
- Established a process to more efficiently update and file certificates of coverage, resulting in the timely distribution of member enrollment materials during the peak renewal season.

Education & Professional Development
CustomerCentric Selling Workshop 2014 CustomerCentric Systems, LLC
Inspirational Leadership Program 2011 Alere, Inc.
Direct Marketing Institute 2011 Direct Marketing Association
Effective Product Marketing Workshop 2010 Pragmatic Marketing
Bachelor of Science: Healthcare Administration 1999 Winona State University City, State
Computer Skills

- Sales: Oracle CRM on Demand, SAVO Sales Enablement
- Marketing Automation: Bronto, HubSpot
- Desktop: Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Acrobat, Reader and Publisher